A Guide to the John H. Knowles Papers FA047
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Massachusetts General Hospital, 1947-1972 1959-1971; 2; 22.6 Cubic Feet
  - Massachusetts General Hospital - Professional, B
    - Pulmonary Clinic - Rounds, 1959-1962 (Box 44, Folder 510)
    - Pulmonary Clinic Project, 1959-1961 (Box 45, Folder 511)
    - Pulmonary Disease Unit, 1957, 1959-1965 (Box 45, Folder 512)
    - Pulmonary Disease Unit - Annual Reports, 1959-1961 (Box 45, Folder 513)
    - Pulmonary Disease Unit - Cardiac Output, 1961 (Box 45, Folder 514)
    - Pulmonary Disease Unit - Forms (Box 45, Folder 515)
    - Pulmonary Disease Unit - Finances, 1954, 1960-1963 (Box 45, Folder 516)
    - Pulmonary Function - Notes (Box 45, Folder 517)
    - Regional Collaboration in Surgical Education for Foreign Medical Students - A Progress Report, circa 1965 (Box 45, Folder 518)
    - Regional Planning - Radio Statement, 1967 (Box 45, Folder 519)
    - Regional Planning Editorial, 1965 (Box 45, Folder 520)
    - Regional Planning Study Committee, 1963-1964 (Box 45, Folder 521)
    - Regional Planning Study Committee - Supplemental Material (Box 46, Folder 522)
    - Requests for Articles and Books, 1967-1969 (Box 46, Folder 523)
    - Requests for Interviews, 1969-1971 (Box 46, Folder 524)
    - Resignations, 1971 (Box 46, Folder 525)
    - Respiratory Center, 1961-1962 (Box 46, Folder 526)
    - Respiratory Failure - Chloride - Swarz, 1961 (Box 46, Folder 527)
    - Respiratory Physiology of Aging - Diffusion Capacity, 1960 (Box 46, Folder 528)
    - Retina/Emphysema Project, 1960-1961 (Box 46, Folder 529)
    - Reuther and Company, 1960-1961 (Box 46, Folder 530)
    - Reviews, 1966-1969 (Box 46, Folder 531)
    - Rhode Island Hospital, 1961 (Box 46, Folder 532)
    - Richmond Area Heart Association - Cardiovascular Symposium, 1961 (Box 46, Folder 533)
    - Royal Society for the Promotion of Health, 1968 (Box 46, Folder 534)
    - Royal Society of Medicine - Anglo-American Conference on Medical Care, 1970-1971 (Box 46, Folder 535)
    - Russell Award, 1969 (Box 46, Folder 536)
    - Russell, Dr. Paul, 1959, 1962 (Box 46, Folder 537)
    - "Saturday Review", 1970-1971 (Box 47, Folder 538)
    - Schweppe, Dr. H. Irving, Jr., 1961-1962 (Box 47, Folder 539)
    - Science and Public Policy, 1959, 1966-1967 (Box 47, Folder 540)
    - Science and Public Policy, 1959, 1966-1967 (Box 47, Folder 541)
    - Science and Public Policy, 1959, 1966-1967 (Box 47, Folder 542)
    - Science and Public Policy, 1959, 1966-1967 (Box 47, Folder 543)
    - Senate Subcommittee on Executive Reorganization - Health in America, 1968 (Box 47, Folder 544)
    - Senate Subcommittee on Health of the Elderly, 1969 (Box 47, Folder 545)
    - Seven Public Health Hospitals, 1966 (Box 47, Folder 546)
    - Simmons College - Commencement, 1969-1970 (Box 47, Folder 547)
    - Social Science in Medicine, 1962-1963 (Box 47, Folder 548)
    - Social Security - Health Benefits, 1967 (Box 47, Folder 549)
    - Society of Medical Administrators, 1969 (Box 47, Folder 550)
    - Society of Urban Physicians, 1969 (Box 47, Folder 551)
    - Space Cadets, 1962-1965 (Box 48, Folder 552)
    - Special Commission on Non-Profit and Medical Service Corporations, 1962-1963, 1966 (Box 48, Folder 553)
    - Stamford University, 1971 (Box 48, Folder 554)
    - Strong Memorial Hospital Report, 1961 (Box 48, Folder 555)
      Restricted material.
    - Subcommittee on Executive Reorganization, 1968 (Box 48, Folder 556)
    - Suffolk District Medical Society, 1964 (Box 48, Folder 557)
    - State University of New York (SUNY) - Downstate Medical Center, 1970-1971 (Box 48, Folder 558)
    - State University of New York (SUNY) at Buffalo - Board of Visitors, 1968-1969 (Box 48, Folder 559)
    - State University of New York (SUNY) at Buffalo - Provost Offer, 1967 (Box 48, Folder 560)
    - Surgeon's Handbook, 1959-1964 (Box 48, Folder 561)
    - Syntex Corporation Pharmaceutical, 1963 (Box 48, Folder 562)
    - Thomas Jefferson University, 1971 (Box 48, Folder 563)
    - Thurlbeck, Dr. W. M., 1958-1962 (Box 48, Folder 564)
    - Travel Expenses, 1970-1971 (Box 48, Folder 565)
    - Tufts-New England Medical Center Planning Process Report, 1965 (Box 48, Folder 566)
    - Unemployment Insurance, 1966 (Box 48, Folder 567)
    - Uniform Rules for Adjudicatory Proceedings Before Administrative Agencies and for Adopting Administrative Regulations, 1966 (Box 48, Folder 568)
    - U. S. Chamber of Commerce - Task Force on Economic Growth and Opportunity, 1966 (Box 48, Folder 569)
    - U. S. Public Health Service - Aging Study, 1959-1964 (Box 48, Folder 570)
    - United States Public Health Special Fellowship, 1961 (Box 49, Folder 571)
    - University Hospitals of Cleveland - Centennial Talk, 1965 (Box 49, Folder 572)
    - University of California, San Francisco - Commencement, 1971 (Box 49, Folder 573)
    - University of California, San Francisco Medical Center - Chancellorship Offer, 1968 (Box 49, Folder 574)
    - University of Connecticut - School of Medicine, 1966-1967 (Box 49, Folder 575)
    - University of Florida, 1969-1971 (Box 49, Folder 576)
    - University of Illinois at the Medical Center, 1969-1970 (Box 49, Folder 577)
    - University of Maryland, School of Medicine - Pincoffs Lecture, 1970 (Box 49, Folder 578)
    - University of Rochester, 1959-1964 (Box 49, Folder 579)
    - University of Rochester, 1959-1964 (Box 49, Folder 580)
    - University of Wisconsin, 1971 (Box 49, Folder 581)
    - Upjohn Company - Grant, 1960-1961 (Box 49, Folder 582)
    - Veterans Administration Contract, 1960-1961 (Box 49, Folder 583)
    - Vietnam, November 28, 1967-January 25, 1969 (Box 49, Folder 584)
    - Vietnam, November 28, 1967-January 25, 1969 (Box 49, Folder 585)
    - Vietnam, July 31-November 27, 1967, n.d. (Box 50, Folder 586)
    - Vietnam, July 31-November 27, 1967, n.d. (Box 50, Folder 587)
    - Vietnam, July 31-November 27, 1967, n.d. (Box 50, Folder 588)
    - Vietnam, July 31-November 27, 1967, n.d. (Box 50, Folder 589)
    - Vietnam - Official Visit Information (Box 50, Folder 590)
    - Vietnam - Official Visit Information (Box 50, Folder 591)
    - Vietnam - United States Agency for International Development (USAID), 1967 (Box 50, Folder 592)
    - Vietnam - United States Agency for International Development (USAID), 1967 (Box 50, Folder 593)
    - Vietnam - Supplemental Material (Box 50, Folder 594)
    - Vietnam - Supplemental Material (Box 51, Folder 595)
    - Vietnam - Supplemental Material (Box 51, Folder 596)
    - Vietnam - Trip Log, 1967 (Box 51, Folder 597)
    - Vietnam - Appraisal Team Correspondence, August-September 1967 (Box 51, Folder 598)
    - Vietnam - Appraisal Team Correspondence, August-September 1967 (Box 51, Folder 599)
    - Vietnam - Appraisal Team Meeting, September 1967 (Box 51, Folder 600)
    - Vietnam - Appraisal Team Report - Draft (Box 51, Folder 601)
    - Vietnam - "Report of the Viet Nam Appraisal Team", 1967 (Box 51, Folder 602)
    - Vietnam - Senate Subcommittee on Refugees, 1967 (Box 51, Folder 603)
    - Vietnam - Notes (Box 52, Folder 604)
    - Vietnam - "Official Visit to the Republic of Viet Nam" - Manuscript, August 1967 (Box 52, Folder 605)
    - Vietnam - "Official Visit to the Republic of Viet Nam" - Revised Manuscript, 1967 (Box 52, Folder 606)
    - Vietnam - "Vietnam - Medicine and Politics" - Condensed Version, November 1967 (Box 52, Folder 607)
    - Vietnam - "Vietnam - Medicine and Politics" - Master Copy (Box 53, Folder 608)
    - Vietnam - Articles, 1967-1968 (Box 53, Folder 609)
    - Vietnam - Clippings, 1967-1968 (Box 53, Folder 610)
    - Vietnam - Clippings, 1967-1968 (Box 53, Folder 611)
    - Ward IV Investigations, 1961 (Box 53, Folder 612)
    - Ward Visits, 1961-1967 (Box 53, Folder 613)
    - Washington, D. C. Trip, 1962 (Box 53, Folder 614)
    - Washington University Medical Alumni Association, 1965-1966, 1971 (Box 53, Folder 615)
    - Washington University School of Medicine, 1969-1970 (Box 53, Folder 616)
    - Wayne State University - Commencement, 1970-1971 (Box 53, Folder 617)
    - Wellesley College, 1962-1963 (Box 53, Folder 618)
    - West Roxbury Veterans Administration Hospital, 1960-1962, 1964 (Box 53, Folder 619)
    - WGBH-TV, 1963-1964 (Box 53, Folder 620)
    - White House Conference on Health (Box 53, Folder 621)
    - White House Conference on Health - Papers (Box 53, Folder 622)
    - White Pines Copper Company, 1959-1960 (Box 54, Folder 623)
    - White Pines - La Croix Hospital, 1959 (Box 54, Folder 624)
    - Wilmington Medical Center - Weiss Lecture, 1970 (Box 54, Folder 625)
    - Yale University Council Committee on Medical Affairs, 1969-1971 (Box 54, Folder 626)
    - Young Men's Christian Association (YMCA), 1967-1970 (Box 54, Folder 627)
  - Massachusetts General Hospital - Personal, C
    Subseries C contains Knowles's personal correspondence with family members and friends, clubs, and private interests, including the Woodstock Service Corporation and his 15th Harvard Reunion.
    - Clippings, 1962-1963, 1969, 1971 (Box 54, Folder 628)
    - General Correspondence, July 1964-1971 (Box 54, Folder 629)
    - General Correspondence, July 1964-1971 (Box 54, Folder 630)
    - General Correspondence, July 1964-1971 (Box 54, Folder 631)
    - General Correspondence, 1959-June 1964 (Box 55, Folder 632)
    - General Correspondence, 1959-June 1964 (Box 55, Folder 633)
    - General Correspondence, 1959-June 1964 (Box 55, Folder 634)
    - Harvard Reunion (15th), 1961-1962 (Box 55, Folder 635)
    - Income Statements, 1961-1971 (Box 55, Folder 636)
    - Insurance, 1961-1966, 1968-1969 (Box 55, Folder 637)
    - Investor's Bank and Trust Company, 1969 (Box 55, Folder 638)
    - Knowles, James, 1961-1964, 1967 (Box 55, Folder 639)
    - Lodge, George Clark, 1962 (Box 55, Folder 640)
    - Massachusetts Bay Investment Corporation, 1962-1966 (Box 55, Folder 641)
    - Somerset Club, 1965-1968 (Box 55, Folder 642)
    - Tavern Club, 1961-1966, 1970 (Box 55, Folder 643)
    - Woodstock Service Corporation, 1968-1971 (Box 55, Folder 644)
  - Massachusetts General Hospital - Manuscripts, D
    Subseries D consists of manuscripts of articles, books, and speeches.
    This subseries is arranged alphabetically by title.
    - List of Articles and Editorials (Box 56, Folder 645)
    - "Acid - Base Balance" (Box 56, Folder 646)
    - "Administration of a University Hospital", 1968 (Box 56, Folder 647)
    - "The Aging Lung and Emphysema", 1961 (Box 56, Folder 648)
    - "The Aims of Education" (Box 56, Folder 649)
    - "Alcoholism and the Urban Medical Center", 1968 (Box 56, Folder 650)
    - "The Ambulatory Clinic", 1964 (Box 56, Folder 651)
    - "The American Doctor" (Box 56, Folder 652)
    - "Analysis of Patterns of Hospital Admissions and Care Using Computer Retrieval Techniques", 1966 (Box 56, Folder 653)
    - "An Analysis of the Pressure Volume Characteristics of the Lung", 1961-1964 (Box 56, Folder 654)
    - "An Analysis of the Pressure Volume Characteristics of the Lung", 1961-1964 (Box 56, Folder 655)
    - "An Analysis of the Pressure Volume Characteristics of the Lung" - Lung Charts, 1961-1964 (Box 56, Folder 656)
    - "Analysis of the Static Pressure-Volume Curve of the Lung", 1961 (Box 56, Folder 657)
    - "Around the Periphery: The Good Ship MGH", 1964 (Box 56, Folder 658)
    - "The Balanced Biology of the Teaching Hospital", 1963 (Box 56, Folder 659)
    - "The Balanced Biology of the Teaching Hospital" - Notes (Box 56, Folder 660)
    - "The Balanced Biology of the Teaching Hospital" - Notes (Box 57, Folder 661)
    - "The Balanced Biology of the Teaching Hospital" - Notes (Box 57, Folder 662)
    - "Beg, Borrow and Steal", 1964 (Box 57, Folder 663)
    - Book Reviews, 1963, 1966 (Box 57, Folder 664)
    - "Boston Magazine" - Commentary, 1970 (Box 57, Folder 665)
    - "Boston's Stake in Medicine", 1962 (Box 57, Folder 666)
    - "Cases from The Medical Grand Rounds of the Massachusetts General Hospital", 1958 (Box 57, Folder 667)
    - "The Challenge to the Teaching Hospital", 1967 (Box 57, Folder 668)
    - "Chronic Non-Specific Pulmonary Disease: Chronic Bronchitis and Emphysema" (Box 57, Folder 669)
    - "Commercial Club" (Box 57, Folder 670)
    - "Community Facilities Development", 1965 (Box 57, Folder 671)
    - "Costs, Deficits and Reimbursements", 1963 (Box 57, Folder 672)
    - "Current Issues Besetting American Medicine", 1970 (Box 57, Folder 673)
    - "Determination of Oxygenated, Mixed Venous Blood CO Tension by a Breath-Holding Method", 1960 (Box 57, Folder 674)
    - "Differences between Ward and Private Medical Patients at the Massachusetts General Hospital" (Box 57, Folder 675)
    - "Diffusion", 1959-1960 (Box 57, Folder 676)
    - "Disorders of the Respiratory System", 1968 (Box 57, Folder 676A)
    - "Distribution of Inspired Air" (Box 57, Folder 677)
    - "Dyspnea", 1961 (Box 57, Folder 678)
    - "Education and the School", 1966 (Box 57, Folder 679)
    - "Education, Service and Money in Hospitals", 1965 (Box 57, Folder 680)
    - "The Effects of Illness on Families", 1964 (Box 57, Folder 681)
    - "The Elimination of Carbon Dioxide", 1964 (Box 57, Folder 682)
    - "The Emergence of the Hospital as a Social Institution", 1969 (Box 57, Folder 683)
    - "The Emergency Ward", 1966 (Box 57, Folder 684)
    - Ether Day Speech, 1962 (Box 57, Folder 685)
    - "Experts, Enclaves and the Public Interest", 1966 (Box 57, Folder 686)
    - "Extrapulmonary Manifestations of Brochogenic Carcinoma", 1959-1960 (Box 57, Folder 687)
    - "Federal Role in Health Affairs" (Box 58, Folder 688)
    - "For the People", 1967 (Box 58, Folder 689)
    - "Freedom Versus Responsibility", 1964 (Box 58, Folder 690)
    - "The Future: Myrrh or Miasma?", 1965 (Box 58, Folder 691)
    - George Washington University Clinic Dedication, 1969 (Box 58, Folder 692)
    - "The Health Center and Alcoholism", 1965 (Box 58, Folder 693)
    - "Health in Vietnam and Urban America", 1968 (Box 58, Folder 694)
    - "Health Services - Producer and Consumer", 1970 (Box 58, Folder 695)
    - "Higher Education and the Nation's Health", 1971 (Box 58, Folder 696)
    - History of Medicine in the 20th Century (Box 58, Folder 697)
    - "Hospitals, Doctors, and the Public Interest", 1970 (Box 58, Folder 698)
    - "The Hospital's Future", 1966 (Box 58, Folder 699)
    - "Hospitals in Crisis" (Box 58, Folder 700)
    - "The Ills of the BCH", 1968 (Box 58, Folder 701)
    - "Impact of Medicare on Medical Education", 1967 (Box 58, Folder 702)
    - "Individualism, Social Welfare and the Frontier in American Life", 1969 (Box 58, Folder 703)
    - "Issues Besetting American Medicine" (Box 58, Folder 704)
    - "It's People" (Box 58, Folder 705)
    - Lahey Memorial Talk (Box 58, Folder 706)
    - "Lowell Institute Lectures at Massachusetts General Hospital", 1963 (Box 58, Folder 707)
    - "Lung Abcess", 1961 (Box 58, Folder 708)
    - "Lung Volumes and Aging: A Review and a Report of Changes in 43 Spanish-American War Veterans", 1964 (Box 58, Folder 709)
    - "The Man the A.M.A. Cut Down", 1969 (Box 58, Folder 710)
    - "Manpower in Ophthalmology and Otolaryngology", 1969 (Box 58, Folder 711)
    - "The Massachusetts General Hospital - A Case Study of Social Welfare in a Scientific Society" (Box 58, Folder 712)
    - "The MGH and the Maintenance of Pre-Eminence", 1962 (Box 58, Folder 713)
    - "Massachusetts General Hospital - Some Contemporary Problems", 1965 (Box 58, Folder 714)
    - "MGH World", 1962 (Box 58, Folder 715)
    - "Medical Care: Its Social and Organizational Aspects", 1963 (Box 58, Folder 716)
    - "The Medical Center and the Community Health Center", 1964 (Box 58, Folder 717)
    - "Medical Center, Health and Dis-Ease" (Box 58, Folder 718)
    - "Medical Education and the Rationalization of Health Services" (Box 58, Folder 719)
    - "Medical Manpower", 1970-1971 (Box 59, Folder 720)
    - "Medical Manpower" - Harvard University Press Edition, 1968 (Box 59, Folder 721)
    - "Medical Manpower" - "Journal of Medical Education" Edition, 1968-1969 (Box 59, Folder 722)
    - "Medical School, Teaching Hospital and Social Responsibility", 1964-1965 (Box 59, Folder 723)
    - "Medical School, Teaching Hospital and Social Responsibility", 1964-1965 (Box 59, Folder 724)
    - "Mental Disease and the Urban Hospital", 1964 (Box 59, Folder 725)
    - "New Demands Harass Hospital M.D.'s", 1963 (Box 59, Folder 726)
    - "The Nursing Home", 1965 (Box 59, Folder 727)
    - "On Hospital Costs and Care", 1965 (Box 59, Folder 728)
    - "On the Coming Health Crisis", 1970 (Box 59, Folder 729)
    - "On the Static Pressure - Volume Characteristics of the Lung" (Box 59, Folder 730)
    - "Papilledema and Respiratory Insufficiency", 1963 (Box 60, Folder 731)
    - "The Pathophysiology of the Pulmonary Circulation in Primary Lung Disease", 1961 (Box 60, Folder 732)
    - "The Physician in the Decade Ahead", 1970 (Box 60, Folder 733)
    - "Physician Shortages in the United States", 1970 (Box 60, Folder 734)
    - "Planning in Complex Institutions", 1962 (Box 60, Folder 735)
    - "Pressure - Volume Characteristics of the Lung", 1959 (Box 60, Folder 736)
    - "The Professor and the Out-Patient Department" (Box 60, Folder 737)
    - "Prognosis of Cor Pulmonale", 1963 (Box 60, Folder 738)
    - "Prognostic Significance of Papilledema in Course of Respiratory Insufficiency", 1963 (Box 60, Folder 739)
    - "Pulmonary Function and Thoracic Surgery" (Box 60, Folder 740)
    - "Pulmonary Function Tests", 1960 (Box 60, Folder 741)
    - "Radiology: A Case Study in Manpower and Technology", 1969 (Box 60, Folder 742)
    - "Radiology: A Case Study in Manpower and Technology", 1969 (Box 60, Folder 743)
    - "The Rationalization of Health Services through Medical Education", 1971 (Box 61, Folder 744)
    - "Red, White and Blue: Vietnam - Civil Strife and Student Dissent", 1968 (Box 61, Folder 745)
    - "Regional Planning", 1966 (Box 61, Folder 746)
    - Regional Planning Statement for Radio Station WEEI, 1967 (Box 61, Folder 747)
    - "Report to 'Committee of Four' of Washington University", 1964 (Box 61, Folder 748)
    - Respiration (Box 61, Folder 749)
      Book notes.
    - "Respiratory Physiology and Pulmonary Function Tests" (Box 61, Folder 750)
    - "Role of the Hospital: The Ambulatory Clinic", 1965 (Box 61, Folder 751)
    - "The Scope and Responsibility of Medicine", 1968 (Box 61, Folder 752)
    - "A Shortage of Doctors", 1969 (Box 61, Folder 753)
    - "Should Nurses Unionize?", 1964 (Box 61, Folder 754)
    - "Social Conscience and the Primary Function of the Hospital Viewed in Historical Perspective", 1963 (Box 61, Folder 755)
    - "Socio-Economic Issues and the Medical Profession" (Box 61, Folder 756)
    - "Spellbinding and Spellbreaking in American Medicine", 1971 (Box 61, Folder 757)
    - "Student Dissent" (Box 61, Folder 758)
    - "The Teaching Community Hospital and the Academic Ideal", 1963 (Box 61, Folder 759)
    - "Therapy in Chronic Pulmonary Disease" (Box 61, Folder 760)
    - "This Office is Like a Blowtorch", 1969 (Box 61, Folder 761)
    - "Tomorrow's Hospital", 1966 (Box 61, Folder 762)
    - "Town, Gown and Ongoing Education" (Box 61, Folder 763)
    - Unidentified (Box 61, Folder 764)
    - "U. S. Health: Do We Face a Catastrophe?", 1970 (Box 61, Folder 765)
    - "The University Hospital as a Community Health Resource", 1966 (Box 61, Folder 766)
    - "Utopia or Dystopia in an Age of Confusion" (Box 61, Folder 767)
    - "Ventilation - Perfusion Relations" (Box 61, Folder 768)
    - "Views of Medical Education and Medical Care", 1968 (Box 62, Folder 769)
    - "Views of Medical Education and Medical Care", 1968 (Box 62, Folder 770)
    - "Volunteerism", 1971 (Box 62, Folder 771)
    - Watershed Papers (Box 62, Folder 772)
    - "Watershed of the 1970's", 1970-1971 (Box 62, Folder 773)
    - "Watershed of the 1970's", 1970-1971 (Box 62, Folder 774)
    - "Watershed of the 1970's", 1970-1971 (Box 62, Folder 775)
    - "Watershed of the 1970's" - Other Versions (Box 62, Folder 776)
    - "What Children Teach Their Parents", 1968 (Box 62, Folder 777)
    - "Where Doctors Fail", 1970 (Box 62, Folder 778)
    - "The Work of Breathing" (Box 62, Folder 779)
  - Massachusetts General Hospital - Printed Material, E
    Subseries E consists of one folder of articles about Dr. Knowles.
    - Articles About Knowles (Box 62, Folder 780)
  - Massachusetts General Hospital - Information Files, F
    Subseries F contains the information files Dr. Knowles kept for reference purposes. Subjects include health insurance, medical education, nursing, mental health, and social problems.
    This subseries is arranged alphabetically by topic.
    - Aging (Box 63, Folder 781)
    - Alcoholism (Box 63, Folder 782)
    - American Academy of General Practice (Box 63, Folder 783)
    - Association of American Medical Colleges (Box 63, Folder 784)
    - Association of American Medical Colleges (Box 63, Folder 785)
    - Cysts and Bullae (Box 63, Folder 786)
    - Duke University Medical Center (Box 63, Folder 787)
    - Frostbite and Hypothermia (Box 63, Folder 788)
    - Future and Philosophy (Box 63, Folder 789)
    - Government and Health Care (Box 63, Folder 790)
    - Group Health (Box 63, Folder 791)
    - Health Insurance (Box 64, Folder 792)
    - Health Insurance (Box 64, Folder 793)
    - Health Insurance (Box 64, Folder 794)
    - Health Insurance (Box 64, Folder 795)
    - Health Insurance (Box 64, Folder 796)
    - Health Planning (Box 64, Folder 797)
    - Heart Disease, Cancer, Stroke (Box 64, Folder 798)
    - Hospitals (Box 64, Folder 799)
    - Hospitals (Box 65, Folder 800)
    - Hospital Clinics (Box 65, Folder 801)
    - Hospital Costs and Administration (Box 65, Folder 802)
    - Hospital Staffs (Box 65, Folder 803)
    - Legislation (Box 65, Folder 804)
    - Lung Disease (Box 65, Folder 805)
    - Marriage Examinations (Box 65, Folder 806)
    - Medical Education (Box 65, Folder 807)
    - Medical Education (Box 65, Folder 808)
    - Medical Schools (Box 65, Folder 809)
    - Medical Schools (Box 66, Folder 810)
    - Medical Schools (Box 66, Folder 811)
    - Medicare (Box 66, Folder 812)
    - Medicare (Box 66, Folder 813)
    - Medicare (Box 66, Folder 814)
    - Medicare (Box 66, Folder 815)
    - Mental Health (Box 66, Folder 816)
    - Mental Health (Box 67, Folder 817)
    - Mental Health (Box 67, Folder 818)
    - Mental Health (Box 67, Folder 819)
    - Mental Health (Box 67, Folder 820)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 67, Folder 821)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 67, Folder 822)
    - Nursing (Box 67, Folder 823)
    - Nursing (Box 68, Folder 824)
    - Nursing Homes (Box 68, Folder 825)
    - Nursing Homes (Box 68, Folder 826)
    - Nursing Homes (Box 68, Folder 827)
    - Nursing Homes (Box 68, Folder 828)
    - Nursing Homes (Box 68, Folder 829)
    - Nursing Homes (Box 69, Folder 830)
    - Pulmonary Diseases (Box 69, Folder 831)
    - Radiology (Box 69, Folder 832)
    - Regional Planning, Editorial (Box 69, Folder 833)
    - Regional Planning, Editorial (Box 69, Folder 834)
    - Regional Planning, Editorial (Box 69, Folder 835)
    - Research vs. Education (Box 69, Folder 836)
    - Smoking (Box 69, Folder 837)
    - Social Problems (Box 69, Folder 838)
    - Social Services (Box 70, Folder 839)
    - Social Services (Box 70, Folder 840)
    - Terminal Care Study (Box 70, Folder 841)
    - Ultrasound (Box 70, Folder 842)
    - Unionization (Box 70, Folder 843)
- Interim, 1971-1972; 3; 1 Cubic Feet